Imagine, us meeting again in this fashion.
まさか　こんな形で会うことになるなんて
All of you are my guinea pigs!
お前ら全員がモルモットだ
Academy City is a breeding farm,
学園都市が実験動物の飼育所
and every last one of you are livestock!
てめえらガキはひとり残らず家畜なんだよ
But right now, the one who holds the key to saving Febri...
でもいま　フェブリを助ける鍵を握っているのは
Long time no see,
久しぶりだわね
my little guinea pig.
実験動物ちゃん
Therestina Kihara Lifeline.
テレスティーナ 木原 ライフライン
A blazing hope is blasting through the city
輝く希望が　この街を駆け抜けるから
闪耀光芒的希望 从城市中起跑
It gives me the strength to hold hands with my trusted friends
いつだって　信じあえる仲間と手を繋ぎながら
无论何时 都与信赖的伙伴们握紧双手
and keep looking for a tomorrow that will satisfy us
心のまま　信じる明日を探し続けてる
相信自己 继续追寻着坚信的未来
A Certain Scientific Railgun
On a crowded street I saw your shape drawing away
立ち尽くす雑踏の中　遠ざかる君を見つめてた
站在繁杂的人群中 找寻身在远方的你的身影
Because we understand the love we share now
分かち合うその大切さ　今は分かっているから
分享彼此的珍贵 现在我们已互相了解
smiles light up around me
いくつもの笑顔が　今日も彩って
无数的笑容如今仍明艳动人
and brighten our days
皆を包み込む そんな当たり前を 守りたい
在我身边的那些习以为常 全都想要守护
I want to protect that simple happiness
Once my dreams start coming true, with the sky as my witness,
動き出す夢を　この空に響かせたら
横空出世的梦想 在空中回响
I will begin to have power over my reality
揺ぎ無い力　現実を捉えてゆく
凭借无可撼动的理想 要将现实捕捉
I had the strength to talk about my fears
弱さ打ち明ける　そんな強さを持ってたから
拥有能坦诚弱小的强大力量
I won't forget when it was that I did
いつの日も忘れないよ　この絆だけ抱きしめて
不论何时难以忘怀 拥抱这份羁绊
I will hold dear the bonds that bind us
and blast open a path to a future I can be proud of
胸を張って　誇れる未来を撃ち貫いてく
都能充满信心 击穿值得自豪的未来
Mugino, come on!
麦野も泳ごうよ
Yeah, later.
後でな
Wah! Are you all right?
大丈夫ですか
Hmm?
Ah, this is great.
気持ちいい
Huh? What are you talking about?
どういうことだよ
In short, it's about saving face.
要するにメンツの問題ね
We can't just sit back and do nothing while being taken advantage of.
まんまと利用されたまま黙ってるわけには行かないの
If you get taken for granted in this world, it's all over.
この世界　舐められたら終わりだし
Being manipulated by bad information is your problem.
Are you not gonna swim?
ガセネタに踊れされたのはそっちのミスだろうが
泳がないんですか
This is fun.
Why should we have to clean up your mess?!
楽しいよ
なんであたしらが尻拭いしなきゃなんねぇんだ
I can't believe you!
こいつらときたら
I told you that you'd get paid for it, so stop complaining!
ギャラは払うって言ってるんだから　一々文句言わないで
You said yourself that you were pissed about being tricked, right?
あんたたちだって　騙されてムカついたって言ってたでしょう
Tch...
We're free to get rowdy, right?
暴れていいんだな
As much as you like.
好きなだけね
What's going on, Mugino? Work?
どうしたの麦野　仕事
Yeah. I'm not very enthusiastic about it, though.
まあ　気は乗らないけど
We're going to go work up a little sweat.
ちょっと一汗かきに行くわよ
What?
That look on your face has gotten better, no?
なによ
いいツラになったじゃねぇか
You must have seen your fill of the darkness this town has to offer.
たっぷりと見てきたんだろう
この町の闇を
Did you lose hope?
絶望したか
Did you get spooked when you jumped into the deep end?
怯えたか　闇の深さに
What did you do? Curse Academy City here?
それからどうした
呪ったか　この学園都市を
And then finally, you realized that I was right?
そして最後には　私の言葉が正しかったと気付いた
Academy City is a test site. All its students are guinea pigs!
学園都市は実験所
生徒は全てモルモット
So?
What did you want to ask?
で　何が聞きたい
Or perhaps you wanted me to pat your head and comfort you?
それとも頭を撫でて　慰めてても欲しいのか
I want to save a friend.
友達を　助けたいの
Huh?
Her name is Febri.
名前はフェブリ
She's an artificially-made little girl,
人工的に作られた女の子なんだけど
and unless I do something, she'll only have seventy-two hours to live.
このままだと　後72時間しか生きていられない
So I want to help her.
だから助けたいの
I know that it was an underground organization that made her.
フェブリを作ったのが暗部の連中だってことは分かってる
I thought that maybe you'd know something about it—
あんただったら何か知ってるんじゃないかって
What are you, stupid?
てめえ　バカか
Friend, huh?
友達ね
After you've had a whole heap of your clones killed,
自分のクローンを山ほど殺されて
you can still go on spouting such nonsense?
まだそんな甘ったるいこと言ってあがんのか
This kid, whatever her name is,
その何とかいうガキも
is just one more guinea pig produced by the darkness of the city!
この町の闇が生み出すモルモットの一つだろうが
If you're going to make it here,
この町で生きていくなら
you either get swallowed up by it and live as cattle,
闇に飲み込まれて家畜として生きるか 闇ごとぶっ壊すか
or you blow everything away, including the darkness.
There are no other choices to be made.
それ以外の選択肢なんてねぇんだよ
That's not true.
そんなことない
Huh?
Sure, I've had a good look at the darkness you speak of.
確かに　あんたの言う闇を覗いたわ
I've gotten a shock from it, and I've even become desperate.
それなりにショックも受けたし ヤケになったりもした
However,
でも　そこから救い出してくれたのも この町で出会った人だった
it was the people I met in this city that saved me.
I have many precious friends, and if it weren't for this city,
あたしには　大事な友達が何人もいて
この町がなかったら　みんなとも出会えなかった
I'd have never met them.
There are many things that disgust me,
ムカつくことも　そりゃあ多いけど
but I still don't hate Academy City.
あたしは　この学園都市を嫌いになれない
That's enough.
もういいや　お前帰れ
Go away.
I'm not leaving.
帰らない
Not until you tell me.
教えてもらうまでは
Who was it that created Febri?
フェブリを作ったのは誰
Who knows?
What is their objective? What is this thing?!
さあね
そいつらの目的は これは何
Tell me!
Please!
教えて　お願い
What if I lie?
嘘だったら
Do I have any reason to tell you the truth?
あたしがお前にホントのことを教える理由があるか
Would you believe anything I say?
あたしの話を　お前信じられるのか
Yes, I'll believe it.
信じるわ
Why?
なぜ
Because I've decided to believe you.
あんたを信じるって決めたから
Hold out your hand.
手を出して
Now, eat it.
さあ　食べてみて
It's just chocolate, nothing added to it.
何も入ってない　ただのチョコだから
What's the matter? You believe me, right?
どうしたの　私を信じてるんでしょう
I said I'd believe you, didn't I?
あんたを信じるって言ったでしょう
Go away.
No. Tell me about Febri.
帰れ
帰らない　フェブリのことを教えて
I don't have anything to tell you!
お前に教えることなんかねぇんだよ
I'm not leaving until you tell me!
教えてくれるまでは帰らない
You're so annoying! Get lost!
うぜー　消えろ
Please, tell me about Febri!
お願い　フェブリのことを教えて
Please!
Ah, you're such a pain.
お願い
マジうぜー
Chemicaloid.
ケミカロイド
If I remember, that's what they called it.
確か連中はそう呼んでたな
They?
連中
A chemicaloid is what Febri is?
ケミカロイドって　それフェブリのこと
It was all just theoretical at the time,
当時は理論でしかなかったはずだな
but those boys must've perfected it.
あのお坊ちゃんたち　完成させたってわけだ
Then they're the guys that made Febri? What's their objective?
そいつらがフェブリを作った奴ね
No clue.
目的は何
知るか　自分たちの存在をアピールしたいだろうよ
They probably want to draw attention to themselves.
Attention?
アピール
There's some kind of event coming up, isn't there?
近々何かイベントでもあるじゃねぇか
Event?
イベントって
The Reach Assembly!
学究会
What do you mean, draw attention?
存在をアピールってどういうこと
What would that have to do with Febri?!
そんなことのために　フェブリは
What would it?
そんなこと
Ha, such is the mindset of the chosen Level 5, huh?
選ばれたレベル5様の発想だな
Huh?
Remember this, young lady...
覚えとけよ　お嬢様
Here in Academy City, just by having a Level 5 nametag on you,
この学園都市じゃ　レベル5って名札をぶら下げとくだけで
even a lab rat like you has lots of precious friends that flock to them.
てめえみたいな実験動物にも
大事なお友達が何人も寄ってくるってことさ
When you find out how deep the darkness goes for those who can't even become lab rats,
その実験動物にすらなれない連中の闇がどれだけ深いか
don't get so scared that you wet yourself,
ビビって小便漏らすなよ　クソガキ
you filthy brat!
Huh? So you met with Therestina?
あのテレスティーナさんにあったんですか
Yeah, sorry. It all happened so quickly,
ごめん　急な話だったから　みんなに相談しそびれて
I didn't have the chance to tell you guys.
So the official name for what Febri is called is a "chemicaloid," then?
そのケミカロイドというのがフェブリの正式名称ですのね
And these people are planning to do something at the Reach Assembly?
その連中が学究会でなにかやろうとしていると
She didn't come out and say that exactly.
はっきりそう言われたわけじゃないんですけど
The guy that Kongou and the others saw,
婚後さんたちが見た　フェブリのことを話してた奴っていうのも
who was talking about Febri, was also at the Assembly site.
学究会の会場に来てたみたいだし
When she said there's an event being held soon,
近々行われるイベントっていうと　それかなって
that's got to be it.
I have to ask though, it was that doctor at the hospital
それにしても　テレスティーナさんに会えたのって
that arranged for you to see Therestina, huh?
あの病院の先生の紹介なんですよね
That doctor's face looks like a plushie mascot.
ゆるキャラみたいな顔して
Who is he, exactly?
あの先生　一体何者なの
He did tell me one other thing.
もう一つ先生に言われたことがあるの
That being?
なんですの
Given the amount of lollipops Febri has,
今の飴の量だと　フェブリに残された時間は
she only has about seventy-two hours left.
後72時間ぐらいだって
Huh? No way!
Oh, no...
嘘　そんな
Seventy-two hours...
７２時間
Uiharu?
初春
I'm going to try screening everyone involved in the Assembly.
学究会の関係者をピックアップしてみます
The administrators and participating students, as well.
運営側と参加する生徒たちも
Uiharu...
初春
You awake now, Febri?
フェブリ　目覚めた
Yeah...
How are you all doing, ladies?
皆さん　ご機嫌よう
We brought something fabulous for you today.
今日は素敵なものを持ってきましたの
Did you find any leads, by chance?
もしかして手掛かりが見つかったんですか
Huh? Oh, no, not exactly.
いえ　それは
I'm really sorry.
申し訳ありません
We searched everywhere looking for that guy...
例の殿方を探して　方々当たってはいるのですが
We haven't been able to find anything worth mentioning.
まだこれと言った発見がなく
B-But in time, we'll find him for sure!
で　でもいずれ必ず見つけてみせますわ
Anyway, we're here for other business today.
それで　今日はそれとは別に
We came to deliver a present to Febri.
フェブリちゃんにプレゼントをお渡ししたくて寄りましたの
A present?
プレゼント
It just so happens that we found a very cute outfit.
実は　とても可愛らしいお洋服を見つけまして
We thought it would look adorable on Febri.
きっとフェブリさんにお似合いだろうと思ってんですの
Oh, really? Isn't that nice?
A present for you, Febri!
よかったね　フェブリにプレゼントだって
All right! Let's open it and see, okay?
よし　じゃあ　開けてみるね
Wow!
Oh, how cute!
あら 可愛い
This is mine?
これ　フェブリの
Yes.
ええ
Mitsuko, Wanna, Atsuki, thank you!
光子　湾内　泡浮　ありがとう
N-No need to thank us! It's just a token of our friendship!
お礼だなんて　本の友情の証ですわ
This is mine!
フェブリの
Yeah, it looks good, it does!
似合う似合う
Febri!
フェブリ
Your face is all red. Do you feel really warm?
顔赤いよ　もしかして熱っぽい
I dunno. My head is foggy.
よくわかんない　頭ぼうっとする
Oh, have a lollipop! Okay?
飴舐めよう　ねえ　えっと
Let's see...
We have to hurry.
急がなくてはですね
Yeah.
Oh?
Oh, goodness gracious!
It's him! The guy we saw at the Reach Assembly site!
この男ですわ　わたくしたちが学究会の会場で見かけたのは
Right, Wannai, Awatsuki?
ねえ　湾内さん　泡浮さん
Yes, definitely.
ええ　確かに
That's him, no doubt about it.
この方に間違いありませんわ
What about the photo?
Aritomi Haruki
It's from the participants list from last year.
その写真は
Aritomi Haruki
去年の学究会の参加者リストです
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki
Academy City Research Assembly
First Prize
Aritomi Haruki...
有富春樹
Oh, he won the Reach Assembly's first prize two years ago.
この人　二年前の学究会で最優秀賞を受賞してます
In fact, he's a regular winner of the top prizes, every year.
っていうか　毎年上位優勝の常連さんですね
Wow! If he's a high-ranked regular at the Reach Assembly...
学究会で上位の常連ということは
It means he's one of the most brilliant people in Academy City.
学園都市でも指折りの秀才ということですわね
This guy?
この男が
I don't know anything about him.
全然知りませんでしたわ
Right. I mean, compared to a high-level esper,
そうね　やっぱり高位の能力者とかと比べると
an ordinary genius doesn't stand out much.
ただの秀才は目立たないから
When you find out how deep the darkness goes for those who can't even become lab rats...
その実験動物にすらなれない連中の闇がどれだけ深いか
Huh? This man...
あれ　この人
It doesn't look like he's attending this year.
今年は参加してないみたいですね
Now that you mention it, I think Yomikawa said something about that.
そういえば　黄泉川先生がそんなこと言ってたわね
About how a lot of the regulars weren't showing up this year.
今年は常連の参加者が何人も姿を見せていないって
Let's see.
えっと
Oh, you're right.
ホントですね　今年に限って参加してない人が何人も
There are many people who aren't participating this year.
There's a chance that some of them are his associates.
この中に　その仲間がいる可能性もありますわね
No relevant data.
該当データなし
That just leaves Lab One.
残るは第一ラボくらいしか
Hey, you!
I can't see!
前見えない
Say, Febri, do you still feel warm?
ねえ　フェブリ
もう熱っぽくない ホントに平気
Are you really all right?
Yeah!
She had a good appetite too. So it looks like we can rest easy for now.
食欲もあったし　一先ず安心みたいですね
Have you been looking all this time, Uiharu?
初春　ずっと調べてたの
Yeah, I just couldn't sit still.
はい　なんかじっとしてられなくて
This Aritomi person appears to have dropped out of school not too long ago.
あの有富って人　少し前に学校を自主退学してるみたいなんです
Hmm... What a shame, huh?
もったいないな
Huh?
I mean, if he was so smart and talented that he won prizes,
だって　賞を貰うほど頭がよくて
才能あるんだったら　もっとまともなことに使えばいいのに
he could use that for something more respectable.
Trying to abduct Febri, being in underworld organizations...
フェブリを攫おうとしたり　闇の組織とか
I just don't get it.
訳わかんないよ
Hmm, yeah, you're right about that.
確かにそうですよね
I only just learned about the Reach Assembly for the first time,
あたし　学究会って初めて知ったけど
but knowing that there are other non-espers who are working so hard,
能力はなくても　頑張ってる人がいるんだって
kinda made me happy.
ちょっと嬉しかったのにな
Saten...
佐天さん
Yes, if you'd be so kind, Yomikawa.
はい　お願いいたしますの　黄泉川先生
Okay.
では
She said that there's not enough evidence to take action.
やはり現状では　証拠不足で
動けないそうですわ
But that's what we expected.
まあ　予想通りですわね
We knew that given the pressure Antiskill is under, we can't expect much from them.
圧力がかかっている以上
警備員に期待できないのは分かっていたことですし
Milady, is there something else bothering you?
お姉さま　何か気になることでも
Yeah, a bit. Something Therestina said to me.
テレスティーナに言われたことがちょっとね
A lot of people have to know about Tokiwadai's Railgun, right?
常盤台の超電磁砲って
やっぱりいろんな人に知られてたりするじゃない
I've gotten to meet so many people as a result of that.
そのお陰で知り合いになった人とかも結構いるし
If I hadn't been Level 5, I was thinking...
もしもあたしがレベル5じゃなかったら
ましかしたら
Would you and the others have become the kind of friends we are now?
黒子やみんなと　今みたいな友達にはなれてなかったのかなって
Oh, come on...
お姉さま
The reason I am so attached to you
黒子がお慕いしておりますのは
isn't because you're the Level 5 Railgun of Tokiwadai,
レベル5の常盤台の超電磁砲ではなく
but because you're slightly unconventional and immature,
ちょっぴりがさつで　お子様趣味ですけれど
kind to your juniors and thoughtful...
後輩思いで　お優しい　御坂美琴お姉さまですの
Milady Misaka Mikoto.
Kuroko...
黒子
Thank you. However...
ありがとう
でも
Don't you dare try taking advantage of me!
どさくさに紛れて　抱きつくな
And don't call me immature!
後　お子様趣味とか言わない
M-Milady...
お…お姉さま　お仕置きの際には容赦なさらないところも　黒子は大好きですね
I also do love how you show no mercy when punishing someone.
Study Corporation?
スタディコーポレーション
Yes. Aritomi Haruki's name came up as one of the company's directors.
はい　その会社の取締役の中に 有富春樹の名前が
What kind of company is it?
Febri, which hand has the Gekota?
何をしている会社ですの
さあ　フェブリちゃん　ゲコ太はどっちの
They seem to do a lot of things,
薬品の製造とか　科学関係を中心に
centering around pharmaceutical manufacturing and chemistry.
This one!
Sure is!
こっち
色々手広くやってるみたいでさ
正解
So, do they have any suspicious facilities?
で　怪しい施設っていうのは
The Study Corp. does own a factory in School District 17.
スタディコーポレーションが第十七学区に所有している工場なんですけど
It's an old factory with nothing unusual about it,
どうってことない古い工場なのに 凄い値段で買い取ってるのが気になって
but the fact that they paid a tremendous price for it bothers me.
That sure does smell fishy.
確かに匂いますわね
If it's a factory, do you think that's where they made Febri?
工場ってことは　フェブリをそこで作ったとか
It's possible that that's where the candy is from.
Which hand?
もしかするとあの飴も
どっち
This one.
Or if we could at least figure out the data for its components...
こっち
せめて成分のデータだけでも分かれば
Looks like the quickest way to find out is to go there and look ourselves.
直接乗り込んで調べるのが一番手っ取り早そうね
But we don't have any time.
時間もないことだし
Keeping Febri's eventual health improvements in mind,
フェブリの体質改善は行く行く考えるとして
getting that candy is the highest priority,
まずはあの飴か
or at the very least, the method of making it.
最低でもその作り方を手に入れる
I can't fail.
失敗はできない
Febri's life is hanging in the balance.
フェブリの命がかかってるんだから
That bridge...
あの橋
Having everyone come back smiling,
何一つ失うことなく
without having to lose anything, is my dream.
みんなで笑って帰るっていうのは俺の夢だ
So work with me, so that it can come true.
だから
それが叶うように　協力してくれよ
Thinking back on it now,
考えてみたら 随分強引で身勝手な話よね
that's quite a pushy, self-indulgent idea, isn't it?
Just because it's your dream,
夢だからって
don't you think about what'll happen if it doesn't come true?
叶わなかったらどうしようとか考えない訳
I guess you just have to believe it'll come true, right?
叶うって　信じるしかないか
Yeah.
What is it?
どうした
There's an intruder in Lab One.
第一ラボに侵入者だ
Intruder? Who is it?
侵入者　何者
I don't know.
分からない
The guard system just went to a Shift A alert.
ガートシステムがシフトAで警戒態勢に入った
Lab One's data security is set to be low.
第一ラボは情報セキュリティを甘く設定した
It is a decoy, after all.
言わば囮だからな
It's unsurprising that someone would come sniffing around.
誰かが嗅ぎつけても不思議はない
If they're just now arriving at Lab One,
今頃第一ラボに辿りついたとしても
it won't interfere with our plans, right?
こちらの計画に支障はないわね
There's nothing in there that'll hurt us if it gets seen, is there?
見られては困る物はなかったよな
All of Janie's data has been relocated.
ジャーニのデータは全て移行した
All that's left is the neutralizing agent data.
残ってるのは例の中和剤のデータぐらいさ
To make sure, I'm going to have a look.
To make sure
様子を見に行ってくるわ
To Lab One?
You'd be exterminated along with the intruder.
第一ラボへ
侵入者と一緒に駆除されるぞ
I don't intend to actually set foot inside.
危険を冒すつもりはないわ
Now that our plan is nearly at hand,
計画を目前にした今
I just want to make sure everything is safe,
万が一の不測の事態もないように 安全を確認しておきたいの
so there are no unforeseen situations.
All right.
分かった
Again, there's nobody here, is there? Damn it!
また誰もいねえじゃねえか　クソが
Just like last time, looks like ultra-bad intel.
前回同様　超ガセネタっぽいですね
You're sure we're gonna get paid for this, right?
これでホントにギャラ出るんだよね
H-How come?
なん　何で
Why are those guys here?
何であいつらがここへきてんの
Don't tell me they knew I was coming and were waiting for me.
まさかあたしが来るのを知って待ち伏せを
Well, doesn't look that way.
って雰囲気じゃないわね
Are they working against the people who made Febri?
フェブリを作った連中と敵対してるの
A feud between underground organizations?
暗部同士の抗争とか
Huh? What's the matter, Takitsubo?
どうしたの　滝壺
Mugino!
麦野
Ha! It's no use, no use!
ムダムダ
As long as Takitsubo has her AIM Stalker,
一度記憶した能力を追跡できる
which lets her track any ability she remembers,
滝壺の能力追跡がある限り
sneak attacks are just impossible!
結局　不意打ちなんて不可能って訳よ
Ability?
能力
Does that mean that someone is moving those powered suits using psychokinesis?
無人のパワードスーツを
誰かがサイコキネシスで動かしてるってこと
But there's no sign of anyone around.
でも　付近に人の気配もない
Remote handling? But even if they were remotely located...
遠隔操作
でも　遠隔って言ったて
It was inside the powered suit.
パワードスーツの中に落ちてたんだ
It appears to be made of the same components
フェブリという子の体を構成しているものと同じ成分でできてるようだね
as those that comprise Febri's body.
Assuming that hair acted as a receiver of sorts for some ability...
あの髪の毛が仮に能力の受信機のような働きをしていたとしたら
And if it did,
にしたって
assuming that one person's ability could move that many of them,
あれだけの数を一人の能力で動かしてるなら
that would certainly take a Level 5's power.
それってレベル5級の力よ
Which means that hair must belong to—
つまり　あの髪の持ち主は
Takitsubo!
滝壺　大丈夫
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I guess I swam a bit too much earlier.
プールで泳ぎすぎたみたい
That was swimming?
Ugh, this is so aggravating! We're out.
泳いだ
ムカつく　帰るわよ
Roger that.
Let's go, Takitsubo.
超了解です
いこう　滝壺
Sure.
Yikes!
やばっ
Takitsubo? Is someone still here?
滝壺　まだ誰かいるの
Nah, it's all right.
ううん　大丈夫　今日の仕事の分は終わってる
The work portion of the day is over.
Oh?
Ah, I'm all sweaty. Let's head back to the pool!
汗かいた　早くプール戻ろう
Sure.
Takitsubo, you probably shouldn't go back in.
そうだね
滝壺はもう入らない方が
They sure did make a royal mess of things, didn't they?
あいつら随分派手に暴れてくれたわね
From the way it looks, there might not be anything even left.
これさもう　何も残ってないかも
Inside there...
あの奥
There's an area that has functioning electricity.
電源が稼働してるエリアがある
Don't move.
動かないで
Try anything funny and...
ちょっとでもおかしな真似したら
You!
あんた
Why are you here?
なぜ　ここに
And sure enough, you're involved in all this.
やっぱりあんたが関わっていたよね
What's going on? Are you in league with those guys?
どういうこと
あいつらの仲間なの
You're the one who told Febri my name, aren't you?!
フェブリにあたしの名前を教えたのはあんたなんでしょう
Hey, would you say something—
ちょっと　なんとか言いなさい
Take that with you.
持っていて
It has the neutralizing agent data on it.
中和剤のデータが入ってるわ
Neutralizing agent?
中和剤
The data on the candy.
あの飴のデータよ
If you act now, there should still be enough time.
今ならまだ間に合うはず
Why are you giving this to me?
何で　あんたがこれを
Sorry. I feel the need to apologize to you.
ソリー　あなたにはすまないと思ってるわ
Yes, I'm the one who gave Febri your name.
そう　フェブリにあなたの名を教えたのは私
I couldn't think of anyone I could turn to besides you.
あなたしか　頼れる相手は思いつかなかった
It looks like my estimates fell short, huh?
私の目算が甘かったよね
But today, there was a disturbance here in Lab One.
でも今日　この第一ラボで騒ぎがあったこと
Fortunately, I was able to meet you here.
ここであなたと会えたことは幸運だった
Now you'll be able to help Febri.
これでフェブリを助けることができる
After that, she can...
あとは彼女を…
I'm afraid not.
無理だね
That recipe data is a dummy.
そのレシピデータはダミだ
You can't save Febri with that.
だからフェブリを救うことはできない
I was wise to have some insurance.
保険をかけておいて正解だったよ
So you were the one who let Febri escape after all.
やはり君がフェブリを逃がしたんだな
Not only did you turn out to be a traitor,
裏切り者が判明した上に　有名人にも会えた
but you met with a celebrity.
Just as you said, this is a fortunate day.
君のいう通り　今日は幸運な日だ
This is the first time we're meeting in person, huh, Railgun?
直接会うのは初めてだね　超電磁砲
The data I procured from you has proven quite useful to me.
君から採取したデータには　色々とお世話になっているよ
Then you must be Aritomi Haruki.
あんたが有富春樹ね
I have to say,
それにしても　わざわざ来訪してくれた理由が
I'm surprised that the reason for you coming all this way
is to save the life of Febri, one of our products.
我々の作品である　フェブリの命を救うためとはね
Product?
作品
Then you really are the ones who made her!
やっぱりフェブリはあんたたちが
Whoa...
Better that you don't use electricity.
電撃はやめた方がいい
You don't want to destroy the real recipe data, do you?
本物のレシピデータまで破壊したいのかい
Nunotaba...
布束
Inject that into Railgun.
それを超電磁砲にうって
It'll only incapacitate her. It won't kill her.
自由を奪うだけさ　死にはしない
Besides, if you do as I say, I'm willing to give this to you.
それに　素直に命令に従うなら
これは渡してもいい
We have no use for it anymore, after all.
我々にはもはや不要な物だからね
I couldn't.
そんなこと
Do it.
やって
It's to help Febri.
フェブリを助けるためだもの
Ha! Even a Level 5 is rendered powerless like this.
レベル5もこうなっては無力だな
I did as you ordered.
命令には従ったわ
Now hand it over.
それを渡して
Ah, you're right.
そうだったな
Wha—
That's enough.
もういいんだ
Febri is nothing more than a spare, after all.
フェブリは所詮スペアに過ぎない
Spare?
スペア
Yes.
そう 我々の偉大な発明品
For our great invention,
Janie.
ジャーニのね
A Certain
Scientific Railgun S
S
Next Episode
Preview
I knew you were involved in this! Why, exactly?!
やっぱりあんたが関わっていたのね
To tell the truth, it's a long story.
一体どうして
To tell the truth
話せば長い物語よ
Once upon a time...
Oh come on now!
昔々
いや　それホントに長すぎだから